Mahmut Taskiran

Android Native & Flutter Developer

Github: github.com/mahmuttaskiran | LinkedIn: linkedIn.com/in/mahmutaskiran | Personal website: mamudo.com
Phone number: +90 546 227 2550 | Email: taskiranmahmutt@gmail.com | Date of birth: 12.02.1994

Martial status: Single

SUMMARY

I am a professional programmer specialized in mobile applications and tools. I have been developing Android native applications with Java and Kotlin, and cross-platform applications with Flutter and React-Native. I have experience developing social media applications (with React-Native and Flutter), IoT applications (with Flutter and Java), sensor-based applications (with Java), WebRTC based applications (with React-Native).

I have been focused on developing my programming skills rather than learning a new programming language. Because I believe that programming is a thinking art, so if I improve my programming knowledge then I can think better.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Java, Kotlin, Android SDK, Flutter, React-Native, Git, Go, Rust and JavaScript.

EXPERIENCES

OBSS - Senior Consultant
Jun 2021 - Still working
Android Application Developer at Akhai

Android Application Developer at Akbank via OBSS.

obss.com.tr akbank.com

PATH - Product and Software House | Istanbul Turkey - Android Developer Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

I was responsible for tuttur.com Android app's development and improvement. Implementation and ownership of new features and refactoring of the legacy codebase.

path.com.tr tuttur.com

ARGELOJI, Istanbul Turkey - Mobile Application Developer June 2019 - July 2020

I have been developed BlueOperation's mobile application for Argeloji. BlueOperation offers RTLS solutions that can actively monitor the location of assets to optimize searching time in a wide range of area facilities such as Airports.

argeloji.com - blueoperation.io

POLYINGO (Mobile Application) - Full Stack Mobile Application Developer

May 2019 - Oct 2020

Polyingo is a mobile application that its users can improve their vocabulary and improve their pronunciation by sharing videos about English words and sentences or watching videos shared by other people. It is my individual project.

play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.polyingopolyingo.com

CEKIRDEK BILGISAYAR, Istanbul Turkey - Mobile Application Developer

July 2017 - May 2018

I developed a mobile application with Java and Kotlin. It is a business opportunity that I met with cross platform application development by developing a social media application with React-Native.

cekirdekbilgisayar.com.tr

OPCON (Mobile Application) - Full Stack Mobile Application Developer

Apr 2016 - Oct 2017

Opcon is a mobile application that its users can create profiles and messaging their contact. But it offers more than a standard messaging application, the difference between Opcon and other messaging application is that Opcon let its users manage their phones by sending notifier to each other.

github.com/mahmuttaskiran/Opcon

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor's Degree | Ege University | Radio Television and Cinema

LANGUAGES

Turkish (Native), English (Professional)